beklo.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Namerific

**Privacy Policy**

_Last Modified: _Feb 13th, 2014 at 04:34AM Pacific Standard Time__

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we may collect, and the ways in which we may use that personal information.

**_Personal Information Collection_**

We 

_may_

collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

• Your Full Name  
• Your Billing and/or Home Address  
• Your Phone Number(s)  
• Your Personal, Business, Domain Registrar, or Paypal Email Address(s)  
• Your Domain Registrar Customer Number(s) or User ID(s)  
• Your Driver's License, State ID Card, or Passport  
• Your Bank Account Information  
• Your Domain Registrar Account Number(s)  
• Your Social Networking Usernames (Skype, Twitter, etc)  
• Your IP Address

**_Using personal information_**

We may use your personal information to:

• Administer this website  
• Personalize the website for you  
• Communicate with you directly  
• Verify your identity and/or location  
• Initiate and/or authorize payment transactions  
• Complete domain name and logo design file transfers

Where we disclose your personal information to agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, we may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.

**_Transaction Privacy After A Domain Purchase_**

Unless you've notified us after a purchase to request transaction privacy via non-disclosure agreement or other similar agreement, Namerific has the full right to print, distribute, copy, display electronically, share, market, discuss, and/or publicize your purchased 'domain name(s)' including logo(s) on Namerific and any other place Namerific deems necessary, such as for the purpose of marketing. Namerific may also pubicize the 'sale' price of the aforementioned purchased domain(s).

**_Securing your data_**

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

This Web site is secured with a GoDaddy.com Web Server Certificate. Transactions on this site are protected with up to 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption.

**_Updating this statement_**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**_Other websites_**

This website contains links to other websites.

These other sites' policies and practices will differ from our own. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**_Disclaimer_**

We believe that maintaining and preserving the privacy of user data is of the utmost importance. However, we cannot guarantee that user information will remain private. We acknowledge that in spite of a committed effort to protect your private information, determined individuals can still develop ways of hijacking information and disclosing it. For this reason, we can make no guarantee against the unauthorized access of private information we attain from you.
